http://www.hellema.com/privacy

Privacy policy | Hellema
TwitterFacebookYoutube
Hellema.com makes use of cookies to support important functions. We also deploy cookies to find out where we can improve the website for a better user experience. For more information see our cookie policy.
X Decline.X Accept.
Engels
Nederlands
Duitsland
a Family Baking Tradition since 1861
search
MenuHomeCookie AssortmentBetter for You assortmentPastry Crisps BlueberryPastry Crisps ChocolatePastry Crisps StrawberrySunbest Breakfast Biscuits CocoaSunBest Breakfast Biscuits Milk and CerealsSunBest Breakfast Biscuits YoghurtSunBest Fruit Bars AppleSunBest Fruit Bars Forest FruitsSunBest Fruit Biscuits AppleSunBest Fruit Biscuits Forest FruitsSunBest Fruit Biscuits NaturalSunBest Multi Grain Biscuits ChocolateSunBest Multi Grain Biscuits NaturalSunBest Yoghurt Fruit Biscuits AppleSunBest Yoghurt Fruit Biscuits Forest FruitsChildren's Biscuits assortmentMilkyUfoEvery Day assortmentChocolate Peanut CookiesCrunchy Cookies CoconutCrunchy Cookies HazelnutCrunchy Cookies PeanutFourre ChocoFourre Choco 500gFourre Double ChocolateFourre LemonFourre StrawberryFourre VanillaFourre Vanilla 500gMadonna HazelnutMadonna RaspberryMadonna VanillaOriginal SpeculaasPeanut CookiesPeanut Cookies 300gVienese Fingers ButteryVienese Fingers ChocolateIndulgence assortmentChokick Chocolate CreamChokick Vanilla CreamCountry Cookies Coconut ChocolateCountry Cookies Hazelnut ChocolateCountry Cookies Mocca ChocolateCountry Cookies Rich ChocolateLondonSydneyPisa Double ChocolateConsumer ServiceFrequently Asked QuestionsPartnershipPrivate LabelHellema World WideNorth AmericaSouth AmericaEuropeAfricaAsiaAustraliaHellema Hallum B.V.Our CompanyOur HistoryQuality & ambitionsDisclaimerPrivacy policyCookiestatementAddress & RouteContact
Home »
Hellema Hallum B.V. »
Privacy policy
Quality & ambitions
Our History
Our assortmentHellema assortment
Our Company
Route & contact
Privacy policyIn this privacy statement we describe why we process your data, how we do so and what rights you have. Such as your right of access, rectification or your right to object to the processing of your personal data. We believe it is important that your privacy is respected and will therefore handle your personal data with care. Together we strive to safeguard the privacy of everyone and at the same time make our service as personal as possible. The privacy statement may be amended, for example, by changes in the law and it is therefore advisable to consult it periodically. Incidentally, where necessary, we always consult with the Hellema Works Council about the processing of your personal data.
Company details
The controller of the processing of your personal data is Hellema, Doniaweg 53A in Hallum. Hellema is listed in the Trade Register under number 01054848. If you wish to contact us in connection with this privacy statement, you can call our telephone number 0518 - 438800 or email systeembeheer@hellema.com.
Types of personal data
Depending on the services and functionalities you use, we may process the following personal data about you:
First and last name
Phone number
E-mail address
Street and house number
Postal code and city
Questions you ask us and/or notifications you pass on to us
Purposes of personal data
When filling in our contactform or registering to receive our newsletter, you leave certain personal data with us. We do not use this personal information for purposes other than those described in our privacy statement. The purposes for which we collect personal data are explained below:
Consumer service: If the cookies have not reached you in perfect condition or if you have questions about our products, we collect your personal data by means of a contact form. However, this form only asks for the necessary information to follow up your message and to inform you about the next steps.
Contactform: If you contact Hellema via the contactform, your personal details will be collected. However, this form only asks for the information needed to answer your question.
Newsletters: We collect and process personal data to inform you via a newsletter. These newsletters contain the latest news about Hellema, relevant services or invitations to events. You can always withdraw your consent by using the unsubscribe option included in every message or by sending an e-mail to systeembeheer@hellema.com.
Duration of storage
Your personal information is kept for a longer period of time by Hellema but never longer than necessary to perform the agreed activities.
Consumerservice: We retain your personal data until we have marked your message as "handled", unless we are required by law to retain your personal data for a longer period of time or if retention is really necessary for the performance of our activities.
Contactform: At the time you contact Hellema via the contact form, the information you send will be stored on the mail server. These e-mails are stored for an indefinite period of time. When the contact leads to a cooperation or to a request for further contact, the data is kept until they are no longer needed for further contact. Data is also stored until we have marked your message as "handled",
Newsletters: The storage of your data is for an indefinite period of time. You can unsubscribe at any time via the unsubscribe link below in the newsletters. If you unsubscribe from the newsletters, we will remove your personal data immediately. We do not store the personal data longer than necessary.
Distribution to third parties
We have made agreements with all third parties so that there are sufficient guarantees for the careful processing of your personal data. If we give third parties access to your personal data, we will only do so if we are certain that they are using the personal data for a purpose that is related to the purpose for which we obtained the data. Furthermore, the confidentiality obligations and security measures required by law will always apply to prevent your personal data from simply becoming known to other parties. In some cases, we may be required by law to provide information to third parties such as the judiciary. We always look at how we can respect your right to privacy as much as possible. If we wish to pass on your data outside Europe, for example because a data centre or our supplier is located there, we will only do so under the conditions set by law. We do this, for example, by means of a contract to which the EU Model Clauses apply. For more information about these suppliers, please contact us via: systeembeheer@hellema.com.
Security of personal data
Hellema uses different systems to process your personal data and the suppliers of those systems can therefore also process your personal data. Only Hellema employees who need the personal data to perform their work have direct access to your data in Hellema's systems.
Right of access, rectification or deletion of personal data
With regard to the use of your personal data, you have the following rights:
You have the right to inspect your personal data. This means that you can request what personal data about you have been registered and for what purposes those data are used.
If you believe that we have incorrect personal data about you, you can have these personal data corrected.
You can also ask us to limit the processing of your personal data, including the time we need to assess your requests or objections.
You can also ask us to remove your personal data from our systems.
You may also ask us to ensure that your personal data is transferred to another party.
We will comply with your request unless we have a compelling, legitimate interest not to delete the data that outweighs your privacy interests. You may make the above requests or object by sending a letter with your name, address, telephone number and a copy of a valid identification document to Hellema Koekjes or via systeembeheer@hellema.com. Do not forget to make your BSN on the copy of the identity document unreadable before you send it. You will receive an answer within one month. You can also submit a complaint about the use of your personal data. This can be done with the Personal Data Authority.
Complaints
If you have any complaints regarding your personal data and the way in which we collect, process, share and store them, you can contact us by telephone or by e-mail. Your complaint will be handled by us if possible and you will receive a response from us within four weeks. You also have the right to submit a complaint to the Personal Data Authority, the national supervisor, if Hellema Cookies does not comply with the above.
Questions and feedback
We regularly review our privacy statement and may therefore change it from time to time. If we do this we will announce this on our website. We recommend that you check our privacy statement regularly to be informed. If you have any questions about the privacy statement, please contact Hellema as follows:
Hellema Hallum
Doniaweg 53-A
0518 – 43 88 00
This privacystatement was last updated on 6 November 2018.
Quality & ambitions
FAQ
Consumer Service
Our History
Our assortmentHellema assortment
Our Company
Route & contact
FAQ
Consumer Service
Our products
a Family Baking Tradition since 1861
Hellema is a unique family business with more than 150 years experience in baking the best cookies and developing successful brands. Old traditions continue with the innovation of the future: the latest manufacturing techniques and high quality assurance systems. Much attention is paid to research and product development. This results in unique products that fit the ever-changing consumer demand. With our flexible company structure Hellema can respond quickly to questions from the international market. Therefore the cookies of Hellema are sold all over the world.
Consumer service
Hellema cookies and biscuits are produced by Hellema Hallum BV and are baked with the greatest care. If you have questions or comments about this website or our assortment, please use the consumer service form on this site.
TwitterFacebookYoutube
© 2013 Hellema B.V.
All Rights Reserved.
